realtruck.com 2013-09-02

# RealTruck's Privacy Policy

  * First of all, thank you for stopping at RealTruck.com!  At RealTruck, we are committed to protecting your privacy. The following document (and yes, we realize this is a long one) explains how we collect and use your information on our website.  It also talks about how, under certain conditions, we disclose this information.

We’ll also explain how we secure your personal data as well as your options when it comes to the collection and use of this information.  By visiting RealTruck.com you automatically accept the terms and conditions described in this Policy.

If you have questions or concerns about your data, please call our Customer Loyalty team at 877-216-5446.

 **Information collection and use:**  
RealTruck collects information to provide a high level of customer service and order tracking.  Our goal is to create a friendly and easy to use website that allows you to shop without having to tediously re-enter personal data.  Please keep in mind that you may visit our site anonymously.

Five main ways RealTruck uses your information:

    * Retain your personal information allowing for easier log in access
    * Retain your truck and other vehicle information for your and our records
    * Provide you with relevant products and information
    * Inform you of product information, news, and promotions relevant to your interests

 **Ways we collect your information:**  
At Registration and during the ordering process. Before checking out and even while placing some items in your shopping cart, RealTruck will require you to enter vehicle information as well as an online registration form. During registration, you will be asked to give us your personal information including your name, shipping and billing address, phone number, payment information (credit card number) and email address.

Additional information required may be your country of residence and your organization’s country of operation so that we can adhere to applicable laws and regulations.  These pieces of information are used for billing, to complete orders and to speak with you regarding your order.  They may also be used for RealTruck.com’s marketing purposes.  If we have an issue with your order, we may use this information to contact you.

If you are using the Bill Me Later® method of payment, the last four (4) digits of your social security number and your date of birth are required.  This information is used only for the Bill Me Later® transaction.  It will not be kept in our files.

A few locations on RealTruck.com permit you to enter your email address for marketing and communication purposes.  These are either to register for a contest or sweepstakes or to sign up for email newsletters and special offers.  Participation in a contest or sweepstakes is completely voluntary.  RealTruck will use information to notify contest and sweepstakes winners and to award prizes. We may and will post on our website the names, photos, videos, cities and states of contest and sweepstakes winners when applicable.  By entering a contest or sweepstakes, you may be opting in to receive our email newsletter and special offers and this will be disclosed in the official rules governing the contest or sweepstakes.  Contest and sweepstake rules are regulations are outlined per event.

RealTruck.com may contact you via email for transactional purposes if you have previously shared that contact information with us on our site, such as when subscribing to our email database, creating an account, or purchasing an item. These messages will be for transactional purposes only, such following up on an attempted purchase, and are in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act.

If you voluntarily subscribe to our Email Newsletter you will receive weekly emails from us about new products, specials, tips and other promotions. If you have an email spam filter please add [newsletter@realtruck.com](mailto:newsletter@realtruck.com) to your safe senders list. If you are currently subscribed to our email newsletter list and would like to be removed, simply click here to Unsubscribe.

RealTruck.com employs cookies which recognize your unique web presence and your access privileges, and track your usage.  RealTruck also uses other web tracking analytical web software such as Google Analytics to track general traffic patterns and preferences.

Through the use of third-party advertising services RealTruck.com may utilize cookies and/or pixel tags to show you relevant marketing messages elsewhere online. These messages utilize anonymous data which may reflect your interaction behavior while on our website, including, but not limited to, products and offers viewed, in-ad browsing and searching, video content viewed, and other anonymous behavioral data. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. To opt out, please [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ "Opt Out").

 **Your Privacy Protection:**

RealTruck takes great steps to ensure that your data is collected safely, efficiently and protected at all times.  We employ several internal and external methods of high security to ensure your personal and financial data is safe from potential fraud.

RealTruck.com is a verified Authorize.net Merchant.  Our merchant seal means that our website is not only protected by secure transaction technology through [Authorize.net](https://merchant.authorize.net/ "Authorize.net"), but that we’ve taken the steps to ensure our environment for collecting your data meets or exceeds their standards for doing business.  Authorize.net is a worldwide leader in the e-commerce industry for over a decade, so you can shop with confidence knowing your credit information is locked down.

In addition to the merchant provided security, RealTruck has added [GeoTrust Secure Socket Layer](http://www.geotrust.com/ "GeoTrust") technology to our website.  This certificate once again enables us to do business securely and efficiently without fear of transmitting any personal or sensitive data unwittingly to the wrong recipient.

Finally, trust our website’s content, images, videos and more with our daily [Qualys Secure](https://seal.qualys.com/sealserv/info/?i=871dc140-a57d-433e-a89d-b81673f0e8f2 "Qualys Secure") scanning technology.  Rest assured you’ll receive no viruses or other bots from our site due to our ever diligent protective online software.  With over 500,000 products online with photos and more, Qualys provides us with the protection needed to keep your computer and our servers safe.

 **Additional Privacy Considerations:**  
We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under age 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not submit any personal information to us, and rely on a parent or guardian to assist you.

You may choose to submit a product review, video and/or photograph of your vehicle or accessory to RealTruck.com. If you post a review, we may ask for your email address and geographic location. If you submit a review, your geographic location will be visible to other users (your email address will be kept private). Also, any personally identifiable information that you submit as part of the review can be read or used by other visitors to the RealTruck.com. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you choose to submit as part of your review.

Bizrate.com is an independent company that permits shoppers to rate their experiences in visiting and shopping at online stores. After placing an order on our website, you may receive the opportunity to provide feedback on your experience. This choice is optional and will not affect your order or service from us, whether or not you choose to provide feedback. [http://www.bizrate.com/ratings_guide/cust_reviews__mid–31176.html](http://www.bizrate.com/ratings_guide/cust_reviews__mid--31176.html)

We use your information internally to complete your order, process it and provide you with an additional customer service you may need.  Your order and shipping information is shared with any manufacturer that you may have selected to purchase from us to ensure you receive your product in a timely manner due to the method of our business.  Our agreement with our manufacturer / vendors and brands ensures that your information is not ‘sold’ or used by these third parties in any way outside of fulfilling your order and providing warranty, returns or any other applicable customer service needed.

RealTruck does not sell, rent, license or disclose any of your personal or financial information to anyone other than to our RealTruck.com affiliates.  Our disclosure to our affiliates is solely to perform the function of processing your order, servicing a warranty or providing customer service.  It’s our promise to you to protect your data and your privacy!

Sometimes RealTruck, Inc. hires third parties to perform marketing and other functions on our behalf.  We partner with these companies to improve the quality of our service and to give you, our customer, the best experience possible while shopping with us.

In the event of a request from law enforcement to disclose personal, financial and order information; RealTruck, Inc. will comply with all investigations.  RealTruck, Inc requires the proper subpoenas and court orders are provided to disclose any information.  We will also release any necessary information when disclosure is needed to protect our legal rights, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements.

Upon your request we will stop sending you emails, disable your account for any purchases or update any customer information you requires.  Please visit our Customer Service page or contact us at 877-216-5446.

 **Policy Updates:**  
This privacy policy applies to RealTruck.com. This privacy policy does not necessarily apply to any offline collection of your personal information. RealTruck, Inc. not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any website not operated by RealTruck, Inc. to which our website links or that links to the Site.

We reserve the right to update this policy at any time.

This policy pertains to user data collected and tracked online and does not pertain to information collected offline.

RealTruck, Inc.  
PO Box 2195  
1307 12th Ave NE Suite 4  
Jamestown, ND 58402  
Phone: 1-701-253-5906 Fax: 1-701-253-5908

This Privacy Notice was last modified on July 19, 2012 RealTruck®
